stevenspass.com 2017-07-04

# Stevens Pass Washington Ski Resort - Privacy Policy

Stevens Pass is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We at Stevens Pass have posted this privacy statement to help you, the user, understand how your personal information will be treated.

##### Information You Give Us

Stevens Pass receives and stores any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with personal information but you may be unable to take advantage of certain features Stevens Pass offers such as purchasing a season pass online or receiving a daily weather e-mail. Information we collect includes, but is not limited to name, age, birth date, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, etc.

Stevens Pass will not sell your personal information to any third party companies or organizations. From time to time, Stevens Pass may send you promotional or news information regarding items we think may interest you.

##### Other Websites Not Covered

Stevens Pass contains links to other websites Strategic Partners. Stevens Pass does not control, and is not responsible for, the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. Please review their privacy policies for further information.

##### Contacting the Website

If you have any further questions about this policy or other practices of Stevens Pass, please contact [info@stevenpass.com](mailto:info@stevenpass.com).

Beginning of dialog window. 

Bike Park season is upon us and we are now open for downhill mountain biking, disc golf, scenic rides and hiking.

Beginning of dialog window.
